Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-8: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-8: Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-8: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-9: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1944-1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-9: Miscellaneous, 1945 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-9: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (1945) ] (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-10: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1944-1945, 1952 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-10: Miscellaneous, 1945 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-10: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-11: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945-1948 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-12: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-12: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-12: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-13: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R79)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-11: Miscellaneous, 1945 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-13: Miscellaneous, 1945 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 11-13: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-1: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1944-1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-1: Miscellaneous, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-2: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-2: Miscellaneous, 1945-1947, 2011 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 36)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-2: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-3: Legal, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 37)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-3: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-3: Miscellaneous, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 38)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-3: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-1: Miscellaneous, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-4, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 39)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-4: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945-1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-4: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-5: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945-1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-5: Miscellaneous, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3935, Folder 40)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-5: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-6: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945-1946, undated (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-6: Miscellaneous, 1945-1950 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-7, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-7: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1945-1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-8, 1945-1946, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-8: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-8: Night Club Boom [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-9: Miscellaneous, 1946 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-9: Wanted- More Homes [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-10: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1944-1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-10: Miscellaneous, 1943-1946 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-11: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-11: Miscellaneous, 1945-1946, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-12: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-12: Miscellaneous, 1946, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 12-13: Miscellaneous, 1946-1948, 1979, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-1: Legal, 1946 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-1: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946, undated (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-2: Legal, 1946, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-2: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-3, 1945-1948, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-4: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946-1947 (Offsite-box R80)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-4: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947, 1953 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-5: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-5: Miscellaneous, 1946-1951, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-6: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946-1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-6: Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-7: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1946-1950 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-7: Miscellaneous, 1939, 1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-8: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-8: Miscellaneous, 1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-9: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-9: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-10: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-10: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-11: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-11: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-12: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-12: Miscellaneous, 1947, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-13: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 13-13: Miscellaneous, 1943-1950, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-1: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-1: Miscellaneous, 1947-1948, undated (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-2 [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-2: Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-3: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947, undated (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-3: Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-4: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-4: Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-4: Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-5: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947-1952 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-6: Legal, 1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-6: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-6: Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-7: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1947-1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-8, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-8 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-9, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-9 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-10, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-10 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-11, 1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-11 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R81)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-12, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-12 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-13, 1948 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 36)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-14 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-15 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-16 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-17 [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-17, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 37)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 14-18 [RESTRICTED], 1948-1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-1, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 3936, Folder 38)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-1 [RESTRICTED], 1948-1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-2, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-2 [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-3, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-3 [RESTRICTED], 1948-1952 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-4, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-4 [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-5, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-5 [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-6, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-6: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-6: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-7 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-8 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-9, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-9 [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-10, 1949-1955 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-10: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-10: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-11, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-11 [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-2, 1949-1952, undated (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 15-12 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1952 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-1, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-1 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-2 [RESTRICTED], 1948-1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-3, 1950 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-3 [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-4 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1950 (Offsite-box R82)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-5, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-5 [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-6, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-6 [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-7, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-7 [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 16-8 [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-1 [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-2, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-2 [RESTRICTED], 1949-1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-3, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-3 [RESTRICTED], 1951-1952 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-4, 1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-4 [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-5, 1951 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-5 [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-6, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Volume 17-6 [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Movie: War Production Board 1941-1945, 1939-1945 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Music, undated (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 11)
  3 audiotape reels: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in tape.
  1 phonograph record: 10 in. Label on side 1: "The March of Time theme song"
  1 phonograph record: 10 in. Label on side 1: "Cut 1-Opening, Cut 2-Closing"
- The March of Time: Radio, 1931 (Offsite-box 4029, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Radio: Index: March 1931 - July 1945 and Scripts: March 1931 - December 1932, 1931-1945 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 3)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 1 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Index Mar. 1931 - July 1945 Mar. 1931 - Dec. 1932"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: January 1933 - March 1935, 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 4)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 2 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Jan. 1933 to March 1935"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: April 1935 - February 1936, 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 5)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 3 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts April 1935 to Feb. 1936"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: March 1936 - September 1936 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 6)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 4 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Mar. 1936 to Sept. 1936"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: October 1936 to November 1937, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 7)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 5 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts October 1936 to November 1937"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: December 1937 - November 1941, 1937-1941 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 8)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 6 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Dec. 1937 to Nov. 1941"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: December 1941 - October 1943, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 9)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 7 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Dec. 1941 to Oct. 1943"
- The March of Time: Radio: Scripts: November 1943 to July 1945, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 10)
  1 microfilm reel: Label on container: "Roll No. 8 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Nov. 1943 to July 1945"
- The March of Time: Surveys, 1941-1950 (Offsite-box 3933, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Television, undated (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage: Election Night, 1948, undated (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage: Promotion and Publicity, 1948-1952, 1968, undated (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage: Promotion and Publicity, 1948, undated (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage Scripts, 1948, undated (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage Miscellaneous, 1948-1952 (Offsite-box 3937, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Television: 1948: Political Coverage Miscellaneous, 1948-1952 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe Continuities, Parts 1-8, 1949, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 2-3)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe Continuities, Parts 9-18, 1949, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 4-5)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe Continuities, Parts 19-26, 1949, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe: Contracts [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe Miscellaneous, 1948-1952, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Television: 1949: Crusade in Europe: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948-1949 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Ballets de France (Never Run), 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Ballets de France [RESTRICTED], 1951-1956 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crime Hearings (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1951-1954 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific Outside Libraries, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific Promotion and Publicity, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Promotion and Publicity, undated (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Scripts: 1-5, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Scripts: 6-10, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Scripts: 11-15, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Scripts: 16-20, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Scripts: 21-26, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Crusade in the Pacific: Miscellaneous, 1949-1953, 1963 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Inside Our Schools (Life), 1949-1953, 1963 (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: The March of Time Through the Years, 1939, 1950:-1953, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: The March of Time Through the Years [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Your Stake in Japan, 1951, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: American Wit and Humor: Miscellaneous, 1952-1954, undated (Offsite-box 3938, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: American Wit and Humor: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1951-1953 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Citizen's View of '52, 1952, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Life in –, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Television: 1951: Life: Inside Our Schools, 1952 (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Political Coverage (Never Undertaken), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Our Living Language, 1952-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Our Living Language [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Randall's Briefcase, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Randall's Briefcase [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Sports Show (Never Ran), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: Sports Show [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: 1952: We the People, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 7-8)
- The March of Time: Television: 1953: News Show: Miscellaneou, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 9-10)
- The March of Time: Television: 1953: News Show: Titles: Air Age [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Art, 1952, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Astronomy [RESTRICTED], 1952, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Atomic Power [RESTRICTED], 1952, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Bangkok, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Baseball, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Belmont [RESTRICTED], 1953, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Berlin, 1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Canada [RESTRICTED], 1952-1953, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Digest, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Dogs [RESTRICTED], 1951, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Education, 1952, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Eisenhower, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Elkhorn, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Formosa [RESTRICTED], 1953-1954 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: France, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Germany, 1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Goa, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Hawaii, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Hawaii [RESTRICTED], 1953, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: India, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: India [RESTRICTED], 1952-1953 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Industrial Town Down South, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Korea, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Kremlin's Problem People, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Las Vegas [RESTRICTED], 1952, undated (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time Television: News Show: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1952-1954 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Levittown, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Levitown [RESTRICTED], 1952 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Make Way for the Queen, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 29)
- The March of Time Television: News Show: Make Way for the Queen [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R83)
- The March of Time: Television: News Show: Malaya, 1953, undated (Offsite-box 3939, Folder 30)